no trades on the account though because
just again like I told you guys I don't
have to trade so the 11-11 account this
is how it remains right now we haven't
taken any trades on it um and yeah we're
going smooth haven't taken any trades on
my personal account
so so no trades on the account because I
missed the trade because look at this
literally look at my alarm it alarm hit
at 2:00 in the morning
9134 look where the
Reyes
9134 at 2: in the morning literally my
entry perfectly but I was sleeping at 2
in the morning last week we took no
trades on the 11-11 account because I
simply you know wasn't in front of the
markets uh the show happened they
broke into my house so I wasn't like
Bully even though you know in the social
media I'm acting like it didn't affect
me it did affect me a little bit but
I've been working on some things I've
been working on some really big things
you do look at this TR trade right here
this is the AUD cat trade that I've been
predicting didn't enter it I've seen a
bunch of you guys that did catch it I
just personally I'm not going to say I'm
scared because obviously I haven't taken
a trade in a long time but I'm almost
being extremely selective because I
don't want my first trade back into the
market in almost a month to be a loss I
wanted to be a win so I'm being very
selective on the trade that I take trade
idea one you guys can say I didn't tell
you trade idea too this might look like
last week's but it's not
[Music]
another week without taking one single
trade literally 23 days in the market
watching it every single day and not
taking one single trade that's what it
takes to be consistently profitable
knowing when to be in the market and
knowing when to not be in the market
sometimes in order for you to make money
in the markets it's better to Simply do
nothing cuz you're saving money for when
the good weeks in the markets come 23
days without taking one single
TR 31 days without taking one single
trade you're probably wondering why
that's exactly what this video is for
the last time that I took one single
trade in the market was on November 15
2023 and that trade earned me
$882,000 in two single days on my
personal account and that same trade I
took on the 11-11 challenge where I made
$2,300 which is my first trade on the
11-11 challenge account and after that
huge $82,000 day guess what happened
next nothing nothing for 31 whole entire
days where it was my longest streak
without taking one single trade now you
may be asking is it because the strategy
doesn't work was the strategy not giving
me opportunities and actually it's the
total complete opposite I don't know if
you guys saw but on my Instagram and
telegram I will send trade ideas on a
daily basis and not only were they
hitting but you guys were catching them
thousands of you guys tagging me every
single day capitalizing off of the trade
ideas that I was putting out there on
social media but I personally myself
simply wasn't entering those trades now
you may be asking why if I was
predicting the markets why wasn't I
entering the trades and the real reason
is because the last month of my life has
probably been the craziest month I have
ever experienced
and it all started with the trip to the
most dangerous flla in Brazil I went
with Steve W do in steiny with a purpose
to give back to a flla and help the
community give them money give them
resources that they need and things took
a turn as we were riding through the
mountains in a scooter with my driver
having grenades around his belt holding
a machine gun and riding a scooter at
the same time things got a little bit
crazy as Steve was giving away money and
giving away Goods we got got cramped up
in a corner and over 200 Brazilians came
to us to pretty much take obviously the
goods that we were giving back but the
necessity of them was just making them
super aggressive and the next day as we
were going to go give back to another
Community we got pranked by some
Brazilian thugs that we had absolutely
no idea what was happening where they
threw us against the ground put machine
guns to our head my phone is actually
still broken from when they slam me
against the ground and that same day
that we were going to leave the word was
spreading around that we were giving
away money to the favellas and to the
community and other bad favellas that
were against the other ones were out in
the look for us luckily we caught a
plane and we got out of there fast but
that was the most terrifying experience
that I could ever experience now I was
still predicting the trades but I was
making sure I was staying alive
throughout the day so my priority was
staying alive and not executing a trade
even though I was still predicting the
trades before I left the hotel I was was
simply not executing them because the
majority of these suras don't have
service in order to plug in a trade and
if that wasn't enough when I landed in
Miami after about a 78 hour flight I had
a quick layover flight to then go to
Vegas and gamble with Dana White so I'm
like you know what I'm going to go home
shower get some new clothes and then get
on this new flight straight to Vegas and
as soon as I walk in through my front
door I noticed that a lot of my
furniture is on the floor and I don't
remember seeing the furniture on the
flooor I don't remember seeing some
cabinets open up was super confused on
what was going on and then when I walked
towards the back of my house I noticed
that I have a broken window and the back
door is open and then there I realized
that they had broken into my house and
they had robbed they had robbed my house
I you know went upstairs they had
completely went through my whole entire
office they took my Rolexes they took my
jewelry they took some cash that I had
in the safe but luckily they didn't take
any other big possessions uh they didn't
take the titles to my cars it didn't
take my two brand new cars that I had
just boughten which is my Rolls-Royce
cullin or my Lamborghini SV didn't take
my drift car didn't take any of my guns
they didn't take my computers they more
took some privacy that I had which was
my home it's the place where I laid my
my head against my pillow and place
where I like to call my my personal
space and it was completely invaded by
some thieves that had broken into my
house and taken everything that was to
value of them but I had to put put on a
poker face and pretend like that didn't
affect me because I was going to go
gamble with Dana White and Steve would
do it the next day so I completely put
that aside that that happened to me and
I go to Vegas with Steve would do it and
I'm gambling there with Steve I'm
gambling with Dana and Steve in front of
my eyes turned $10,000 into half a
million dollar we just won Dana 500
Grand because Dana White was down half a
million dollars from a bad gambling
night and he had has really good
relationship with r rooc Casino so he
could you know pay off those markers
whenever he wants but Steve is such a
good guy and he's somebody that will
give back no matter what he loves DOA so
much and you know they do a lot for each
other that he deposited 10,000 and ran
it up to half a million dollar where
then he paid off Dana White's half a
million dollar death now Dana White
doesn't need half a million dollars
that's pennies to the men but it's more
of the act that Steve will do that to
show his gratitude and his appreciation
to Dana White and experiments and being
there for that whole entire live stream
it's very hard to kind of catch a trade
when your time zones are all messed up
you just got robbed and then you almost
got killed in the favet so it's a it's
an accumulation of stuff that I
personally can't execute a trade but I
can still predict the markets because
I'm seeing the same patterns time and
time and time and time again so I can
still send the trades out there but the
execution part I just didn't feel
comfortable putting money at risk at
that very moment and if that wasn't
enough I decided to challenge myself to
do something new and it's put out there
the real Alex the new content of who
Alex really is and for that requires the
wisdom of Alex the facts the
masculinity the truth of who I was to
get to the point where I am today and
everything that happens behind the
scenes of a quick trading video that you
guys see on Instagram that's why I
challenge myself to come out with a new
YouTube channel which is going to be
called Alex was here and this channel is
going to consist of the real life of
what Alex does everything behind the
scenes no filter everything completely
unscripted and you guys can live what I
live through a lens and see the reality
of what it is to be me I think the
social media presence that I have gotten
right now deserves that because
Everything Is Not What It Seems and I
feel it's good so you guys see all the
work and all the time that gets put
behind these videos and gets put behind
the lifestyle to even just make it seem
normal to you guys so this is going to
be be on my second YouTube channel where
everything that I just told you about I
was luckily enough to have my film crew
with me where they documented every
single second of it and all of that is
going to be posted on my second YouTube
channel which is going to be called Alex
was here and as I get back to Miami to
film all this new content I didn't feel
at home in my other home I literally
felt violated my privacy my my my home
they had broken into and they had taken
my stuff so I took action very fast and
I decided to move into this brand new
house that I just moved into now and
this is now probably the biggest and
craziest house I have ever been or
stepped foot inside of and this is now
my new home and a house tour of this
house is going to be on that second
Channel as well so make sure you guys
check it out because by the time this
video is uploaded that second YouTube
channel is already up with all of these
videos and if that wasn't a lot
which it's a lot it's a lot to do in 31
days and on top of that keep the
community going do the rec call of my
students I have something very big
cooking I've been cooking up something
very big that nobody's ever done before
and you guys are going to see it very
soon but that as well is going to be on
the second Channel and you guys are
going to be able to see what it really
takes behind all of the stuff that I'm
doing I get it excites me you guys you
guys can see the reality of who Alex is
that's why Alex was here is going to be
the name of the second YouTube G and
just to wrap things up in the last 30
days of my life I got bit by a snake I
don't know if you guys can see it right
here but in one of Steve will do his
stream Steve pretty much bet me that I
wouldn't let the viper bite me and it
did luckily it did nothing but going
back and forth from Vegas gambling Dana
White again where he was literally
mentoring me how to gamble now I know a
little bit about gambling I know
Blackjack I know back rat but he was
literally telling me what to bet how to
split and how to double down on which is
a great experience but that went on for
hours plus the 3-hour different time
zone of Vegas completely messed up my
focus that week for trading so every
single week has been something new and
it's been non-stop for 31 days and
everything that I have just mentioned to
you guys absolutely everything that I've
just mentioned has been documented it's
been a perfect timing it's filmed the
good it's filmed the bad but it's going
to be shown to you guys because this has
been one of the most hectic and busiest
months I don't think of the year I think
of my life to be completely honest I
don't even know how I held up and to add
like if this wasn't enough I had just
came out of a dark mode right before I
had entered this whole entire crazy
month where I had turned into a pretty
much a new person after I blew the
$300,000 where I turned $100 to 300
which was my goal to turn into a million
where I had set a new goal where if I'm
not in the mindset to trade and if I'm
not in the right position to execute a
trade I simply won't do it and you know
what I put that into effect to
Perfection during these last 31 days and
it could have not worked perfectly I
could have not been more real to myself
and kept the word more than what I have
currently done so although I analyze the
markets I predict the moves time and
time again there's hundreds of messages
that I get on a daily basis there's tens
if not 20 30 free trade ideas in the
free telegrams that I have below
literally I stuck to my word by just
simply focusing on myself when I was
ready to take a trade when the market
was right sometime the market was right
but I wasn't ready sometimes I was ready
but the market it was already if we
simply both don't align I simply don't
take a trade and by having this mindset
and sticking to my word this is what led
me to not taking a trade for 31 days but
all of this has ended on Friday December
15th on this day two very important
things have happened the first one is we
had broken the streak of no trades and
coincidentally enough it was pretty much
the first day out of the whole entire 31
days where I was alone in my home which
is great cuz I got to spend time with
myself and then the second thing is that
not only did we just break out of the no
trading streak but it was an amazing win
that was executed on Euro AUD where I
positioned a 75 lot trade on a sale
where I ended up risking about anywhere
from $30 to $40,000 on the trade and it
had played out extremely well where I
ended up making
$75,000 in one single session and
obviously the same trade that I took on
my personal account that led me to make
$75
I took it on the 1111 challenge where I
had finally taken the second trade on it
because I hadn't taken a trade since I
had originally started it on 1111 so I
was about 33 days without taking a trade
on the 1111 challenge after my first win
this is the challenge that I started
with
$1,111 and I have only taken one trade
prior to the one that I took on Friday
currently right now the account is
sitting on
$633 4 this is literally on two trades
in over 31 days on that account and the
objective of this account is to
literally take it as high as I possibly
can my goal is to scale it to whatever
the market can led me to do it that's a
mistake that I did with the 100 to the
mill challenge which was setting a hard
target now with this 11-11 challenge I'm
just letting time and the market give me
the opportunity and if I happen to align
with it I take the trade and I scale it
to as high as I possibly can and on top
of that probably more importantly to me
because the money that I make on The
Challenge is cool but the impact that I
have on you guys is not as important to
me because I won't take one trade on the
1111 account that I don't send out to
you guys first I sent out you guys the
trade idea first after then I take
execution on it and seeing you guys
learn from my strategy execute it I make
profits by far is way more exciting than
you guys can ever imagine yes numbers on
a screen is cool but seen one of you
guys out there having having a job and
making more money from Trading than your
actual job that is the real word of
success to me I feel like my job has
been complete and by the time you guys
are seeing this video all of the videos
of what has happened in the last 31 days
are already Live on YouTube so search up
Alex was here which is my second YouTube
channel where you guys are going to
literally see what everything that I
just said was in real time so as of
right now the 1111 challenge has
completely come back to life I'm going
to try and turn these $1,100 with $11
all the way up to pretty much Infinity
to the highest that I possibly can 31
days put to sleep now we're bringing it
back to life so you guys are able to Now
Catch the trades with me and I'm able to
scale this account to as high as I
possibly can I have a number in mind but
I can't put it out there because I'm
just going to keep focusing and staying
true to the trades and by the time you
guys are seeing this video everything
that I have just explained on what has
happened to me in the last 31 days it's
all already Live on YouTube so go search
up the second YouTube channel Channel
which is Alex was here so you're able to
see what I'm actually expressing to you
guys because absolutely everything was
documented so it can be put out there
for you guys and with that being said if
you want to know what set and forget is
and how thousands of the Traders are
catching the trades with me catching the
trades even without me click the link in
the description below I have a video
that explains to you what s and frot is
it is what has changed Traders lives
completely where lets him make anywhere
from $1,000 to $11,500 a week as a
beginner set and forget Trader this is
something that has not only worked for
people that have a full-time job but
people can use it to have also a side
income from Trading so if you want to
know what set and forget is and if it
even makes sense for you just click the
link in the description below it's a
completely free video that will explain
to you what it is and how I came up with
it and how it lets me make numbers like
these and like these every single day so
I appreciate you guys watching this
video all the way to the end and I'll
see you guys either in the next video
here or on my second Channel see you
guys